<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-04-01T14:23:46+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">BEF-China</title><subtitle>Biodiversity and Ecosystem Functioning Experiment in Subtropical Forest in China</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Directed species loss from species-rich forests strongly decreases productivity</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/natureEcology/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Directed species loss from species-rich forests strongly decreases productivity" /><published>2020-03-12T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-03-12T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/natureEcology</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/natureEcology/">&lt;p&gt;At high species richness, directed loss, but not random loss, of tree species strongly decreases forest productivity. An international research team with the involvement of the Universities of Zurich and Halle-Wittenberg has evaluated the data from subtropical forests planted in southeastern China with more than 200,000 woody plants. The results highlight the importance of conserving biodiversity in species-rich ecosystems, and warns us that previous studies based on random species loss could bias our predictions of how more realistic extinction scenarios are likely to affect ecosystem functioning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The forest biodiversity experiment, BEF-China, began in 2009 with the collaboration among institutions in China, Germany and Switzerland. The international team simulated both random and directed species extinction scenarios along richness gradients from 16 to 1 species.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After eight years, directed species loss in species-rich forest ecosystems, in which evolutionary distinct species had higher extinction risks, showed much stronger reductions in forest productivity than did treatments that were subject to random species loss. “These findings have significant implications for biodiversity conservation and climate mitigation, because more productive forests also removed more carbon dioxide from the air”, says Prof. Bernhard Schmid of the University of Zurich, senior author of the current publication in Nature Ecology &amp;amp; Evolution. “Our results suggest that species loss can severely hamper ecosystem functioning already at high species richness, when many species still remain in the ecosystem. It challenges the decade-long assumption derived from studies based on random species loss. This assumption was that species loss from high-diversity communities would have only little impact on ecosystem functioning, because the remaining species could take over the functions of extinct species due to species redundancy.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why could directed species loss lead to such strong productivity reduction? “We think two processes associated with directed species loss might lead to the results,” explains Dr. Yuxin Chen, now associate professor at Xiamen University in China and the first author of the current publication. “When species loss is directed, we may lose the most functionally distinct species first, if that functionally distinctiveness is also the cause of extinction. Species do not live independently, but participate in complex networks of species interactions. Losing species can change these interaction networks. The loss of species interactions contributed significantly to the observed results.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ongoing impacts of a severe coronavirus epidemic this winter has prompted China to speed up biosecurity legislation and elevate it to a national security issue. The biosecurity law would cover various areas including conserving biodiversity. “Our research is grounded in one of the diversity hotspots in China. The findings are timely for supporting the legislation of biosecurity. Diversity loss from species-rich forests could also increase the risk of pest and disease outbreaks. Some other research teams are studying this issue at BEF-China” says Prof. Keping Ma of the Chinese Academy of Sciences, co-founder of the BEF-China experiment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Literature：
Yuxin Chen, Yuanyuan Huang, Pascal A. Niklaus, Nadia Castro-Izaguirre, Adam Thomas Clark, Helge Bruelheide, Keping Ma, Bernhard Schmid. Directed Species Loss Reduces Community Productivity in a Subtropical Forest-Biodiversity Experiment. March 2, 2020. Nature Ecology &amp;amp; Evolution. Doi: 10.1038/s41559-020-1127-4&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>sal</name></author><category term="featured" /><summary type="html">At high species richness, directed loss, but not random loss, of tree species strongly decreases forest productivity. An international research team with the involvement of the Universities of Zurich and Halle-Wittenberg has evaluated the data from subtropical forests planted in southeastern China with more than 200,000 woody plants. The results highlight the importance of conserving biodiversity in species-rich ecosystems, and warns us that previous studies based on random species loss could bias our predictions of how more realistic extinction scenarios are likely to affect ecosystem functioning.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/img/siteA2016.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Growth-trait relationships depend on species richness in subtropical forest</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/JEcology/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Growth-trait relationships depend on species richness in subtropical forest" /><published>2020-01-06T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-01-06T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/JEcology</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/JEcology/">&lt;p&gt;The Editor’s Choice article for Volume 108 Issue 1 is “Growth–trait relationships in subtropical forest are stronger at higher diversity“ by Bongers et al. This study assessed how growth–trait relationships at the individual tree level are impacted by species richness at community and local neighbourhood scales.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Editor’s Choice article highlights the impact that species richness can have on functional trait values and their effect on individual tree growth. Using a planted forest biodiversity experiment, this research shows that growth‐trait relationships are stronger at higher levels of plot richness. This creates a larger difference between acquisitive and conservative growth strategies at higher richness, when compared to lower richness or monoculture plots.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The diversity‐dependent growth‐trait relationships observed in this study show that plant growth depends on local conditions created by neighbour identity, size or traits. In order to determine how functional traits shape biodiversity–ecosystem functioning relationships, it is important to consider the biotic context of individual trees within a community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These results are part of a large forest biodiversity-ecosystem functioning experiment in China (BEF China).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This video podcast recorded by author, Xiaojuan Liu, explains their research in more detail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PGjKKOZ4nwY&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/jecology.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;vedio&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1111/1365-2745.13242&quot;&gt;Literature&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Xiaojuan</name></author><category term="sticky" /><summary type="html">The Editor’s Choice article for Volume 108 Issue 1 is “Growth–trait relationships in subtropical forest are stronger at higher diversity“ by Bongers et al. This study assessed how growth–trait relationships at the individual tree level are impacted by species richness at community and local neighbourhood scales.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/img/jecology.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Herbivore Phylogenetic Diversity Can Be Affected By Plant Diversity Loss</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/JEcology_zhu/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Herbivore Phylogenetic Diversity Can Be Affected By Plant Diversity Loss" /><published>2019-08-24T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2019-08-24T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/JEcology_zhu</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/JEcology_zhu/">&lt;p&gt;ZHU Chaodong&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Global change leads to increasing biodiversity loss, usually with consequences for the structure and functioning of ecosystems, such as primary productivity and nutrient cycling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Previous work has emphasized strong linkages between the loss of plant species richness and declines in consumer abundance and diversity. However, the mechanisms underlying these linkages are still unclear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A joint research team integrated multiple components of plant and herbivore diversity, with a particular focus on phylogenetic diversity, to identify the linkages that drive biodiversity relationships and determine the consequences of biodiversity loss across different trophic levels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The team includes researchers from the Institute of Zoology (IOZ) and the Institute of Botany under the Chinese Academy of Sciences (CAS) and the University of Goettingen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These analyses are based on the largest tree diversity experiment in the world at present and make use of an extensive data set that covers herbivore phylogenetic diversity - a diversity component that so far is rarely available for larger-scale analyses of plant-herbivore interactions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The study showed that lepidopteran phylogenetic diversity was significantly affected by plant species loss, but only when basic splits in the evolutionary history were considered. Moreover, using structural equation modeling, the results suggested that multiple components of tree diversity could synergistically affect species richness and phylogenetic diversity of lepidopteran larvae.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Importantly, plant diversity effects were indirectly mediated by herbivore abundance - which sheds light on the consequences of recently observed declines in the number of insects for the structuring and functioning of ecosystems, including evolutionary dependencies between plants and their herbivore communities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The study, published in &lt;a href=&quot;https://besjournals.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/1365-2745.13273&quot;&gt;Journal of Ecology&lt;/a&gt; on August 20, was supported by the Strategic Priority Research Program of the Chinese Academy of Sciences, the National Science Fund for Distinguished Young Scholars, CAS President’s International Fellowship Initiative and other programs to ZHU Chaodong’s Lab.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>sal</name></author><category term="featured" /><summary type="html">ZHU Chaodong</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/img/zhujecology.png" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Species-Rich Forests Store Twice as much Carbon as Monocultures</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/science/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Species-Rich Forests Store Twice as much Carbon as Monocultures" /><published>2018-10-25T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2018-10-25T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/science</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/science/">&lt;p&gt;Species-rich subtropical forests can take up on average twice as much carbon as monocultures. An international research team with the involvement of the University of Zurich has evaluated data from forests grown specifically for this purpose in China with a total of over 150,000 trees. The results speak in favor of using many different tree species during reforestation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2009, BEF-China began as a unique forest biodiversity experiment in collaboration between institutions in China, Germany and Switzerland. The large-scale project investigated the importance of tree species richness for the good functioning of forest ecosystems. Stands of trees comprising different numbers of species were planted – from monocultures to highly species-rich plots with 16 different tree species on an area of 670 square meter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After eight years, such species-rich forest plots stored an average of 32 tons of carbon per hectare in aboveground biomass. By contrast, monocultures averaged only 12 tons of carbon per hectare – less than half as much. During photosynthesis, the plants absorb carbon dioxide from the atmosphere and convert the carbon to biomass. When a forest stores more carbon, this helps reduce greenhouse gases and at the same time also indicates high forest productivity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Biodiverse forests are more productive
The fact that biodiversity increases productivity had previously been demonstrated through exper-iments in grassland ecosystems in Europe and the USA. By contrast, since it was assumed that all tree species occupy similar ecological niches, a minimal effect of biodiversity was conjectured for forests. Evidently, however, this assumption was wrong. “In the forest biodiversity experiment, biomass increased just as quickly with species richness as it did in the meadow ecosystems. As a result, even after just four years, there were clear differences between the monocultures and the species-rich forests,” explains Prof. Helge Bruelheide of the Martin Luther University Halle-Wittenberg, co-director of the German Centre for Integrative Biodiversity Research (iDiv), which together with the Institute of Botany of the Chinese Academy of Sciences oversaw the field experiments. These differences grew continuously over further four years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“These findings have great ecological and economic significance,” says Prof. Bernhard Schmid of the University of Zurich, senior author in the more than 60-strong writing team of the current publication in Science. A previous study already found a positive correlation between biodiversity and carbon storage. However, it was based on simple comparison of natural plots varying in species richness. “Therefore, it was impossible to conclude that higher biodiversity was the cause of the higher productivity. But now we have reached the same conclusion with an experiment under controlled conditions: a forest with a large number of tree species is more productive than a monoculture,” adds Prof. Dr. Keping Ma of the Chinese Academy of Sciences and co-manager of the project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Higher productivity, better climate protection
Worldwide, there are plans for major reforestation programs with the aim of protecting the climate through the planting of new forests. In China alone, between 2010 and 2015, 1.5 million hectares of new forest were planted each year, although mainly with fast-growing monocultures. “Our new study shows that forests are not all the same when it comes to climate protection: monocultures achieve not even half of the desired ecosystem service. The full level of carbon sequestration and thus mitigation of global warming can only be achieved with a mix of species. In addition, species-rich forests also contribute towards protecting the world’s threatened biodiversity,” ex-plains Bernhard Schmid. “Unfortunately, there’s still a widespread misconception that productivity and biodiversity are mutually exclusive, but the opposite is true.” Species-rich forests are also less vulnerable when it comes to diseases or extreme weather events, which are becoming increasingly frequent as a result of climate change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the effects observed in the experiment are extrapolated to the world’s existing forests, it can be concluded that a 10% decline in tree species would lead to production losses of 20 billion US dollars, worldwide, per year. This result shows that, according to the researchers, reforestation with a mix of different species also pays off economically.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Literature:
Yuanyuan Huang et al.: Impacts of species richness on productivity in a large-scale subtropical forest experiment, Science, 5 October 2018. DOI: 10.1126/science.aat6405&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>sal</name></author><category term="featured" /><summary type="html">Species-rich subtropical forests can take up on average twice as much carbon as monocultures. An international research team with the involvement of the University of Zurich has evaluated data from forests grown specifically for this purpose in China with a total of over 150,000 trees. The results speak in favor of using many different tree species during reforestation.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/img/siteA.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Species-Rich Forests Better Compensate Environmental Impacts</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Procedings/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Species-Rich Forests Better Compensate Environmental Impacts" /><published>2018-08-22T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2018-08-22T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Procedings</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Procedings/">&lt;p&gt;To offset CO2 emissions, China is reforesting. If a mixture of tree species instead of monocultures were planted, much more carbon could be stored. An international team including UZH researchers has shown that species-rich forest ecosystems take up more CO2 from the atmosphere and store more carbon in biomass and soil, making them more effective against climate change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/gts_5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; /&gt;
One of 27 forest allotments in the province of Zhejiang in subtropical southeastern China. (Image: XXX)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Forest ecosystems are elementary for a climatic balance. Countries such as China have recognized this fact; for years, they have been conducting extensive afforestation programs to compensate their rising CO2 emissions. As part of the global carbon cycle, forests take up about 45 percent of the carbon from the environment and bind it in the soil and as biomass over long periods of time. At the same time, trees can take up or release carbon in the short term, as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Until now, however, there has been little research into whether the number of tree species in a forest has an influence on the carbon cycle in the ecosystem. A team of researchers from Switzerland, Germany and China has now collated comprehensive data on 27 forest allotments in the province of Zhejiang in subtropical southeastern China for a period of six years. The researchers, including some from UZH – investigated the amount of long-term, stored carbon (C stock) and the short-term carbon exchange (C flux). The forest allotments were chosen to represent a richness gradient ranging from three to 20 tree species and an age range from 22 to 116-year-old tree stands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each additional species contributes 6.4 percent higher carbon stores
Previous afforestation efforts in China have already contributed considerably to reducing the increase in carbon dioxide in the atmosphere. “However, China has limited its program to monocultures,” explains Bernhard Schmid, professor of environmental sciences at the University of Zurich. “We wanted to find out whether a mixture of tree species compensates more carbon than just a single tree species.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The researchers discovered that species-rich forests have a faster carbon cycle than those with just a few species. With increased species richness, more carbon is stored both above and below ground in trunks, roots, deadwood, mold and soil. Estimations of the team of researchers have shown that 6.4 percent more carbon can be compensated with each additional tree species in an allotment. In addition, older trees accumulate more carbon than younger ones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$300 million a year blown out into the atmosphere
“Projected to all of China, additional carbon at a value of $300 million a year could have been absorbed from the atmosphere from 1977 to 2008 if species-rich allotments with 10 tree species had been planted instead of monocultures,” says Bernhard Schmid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To reduce the atmospheric CO2 impact, the researchers therefore suggest planting species-rich tree mixtures in global reforestation programs as much as possible instead of using monocultures. The goals of fighting against global warming and preventing further loss of biodiversity in forests could thus be reached at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Literature:
Xiaojuan Liu, Stefan Trogisch, Jin-Sheng He, Pascal A. Niklaus, Helge Bruelheide, Zhiyao Tang, Alexandra Erfmeier, Michael Scherer-Lorenzen, Katherina A. Pietsch, Bo Yang, Peter Kühn, Thomas Scholten, Yuanyuan Huang, Chao Wang, Michael Staab, Katrin N. Leppert, Christian Wirth, Bernhard Schmid and Keping Ma. Tree species richness increases ecosystem carbon storage in subtropicalforests. Proceedings of the Royal Society B, 22 August 2018, DOI: 10.1098/rspb.2018.1240&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>sal</name></author><category term="featured" /><summary type="html">To offset CO2 emissions, China is reforesting. If a mixture of tree species instead of monocultures were planted, much more carbon could be stored. An international team including UZH researchers has shown that species-rich forest ecosystems take up more CO2 from the atmosphere and store more carbon in biomass and soil, making them more effective against climate change.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/img/gts_6.jpeg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">2020</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020XGS/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="2020" /><published>2018-03-01T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2018-03-01T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020XGS</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020XGS/">&lt;p&gt;Franca J. Bongers, Bernhard Schmid, Zhenkai Sun, Yin Li, Werner Härdtle, Goddert von Oheimb, Ying Li, Shan Li, Michael Staab, Keping Ma, and Xiaojuan Liu. 2020. Growth-trait relationships in subtropical forest are stronger at higher diversity. Journal of Ecology. in publish. &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1038/s41559-020-1127-4&quot;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1111/1365-2745.13242&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Simone Cesarz, Dylan Craven, Harald Auge, Helge Bruelheide, Bastien Castagneyrol, Andy Hector, Hervé Jactel, Julia Koricheva, Christian Messier, Bart Muys, Michael J. O’Brien, Alain Paquette, Quentin Ponette, Catherine Potvin, Peter B. Reich, Michael Scherer-Lorenzen, Andrew R. Smith, Kris Verheyen, and Nico Eisenhauer. 2020. Biotic and abiotic drivers of soil microbial functions across tree diversity experiments. bioRxiv. in publish. &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1038/s41559-020-1127-4&quot;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1101/2020.01.30.927277&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yuxin Chen, Yuanyuan Huang, Pascal A. Niklaus, Nadia Castro-Izaguirre, Adam Thomas Clark, Helge Bruelheide, Keping Ma, and Bernhard Schmid. 2020. Directed species loss reduces community productivity in a subtropical forest biodiversity experiment. Nature Ecology &amp;amp; Evolution. in publish. &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1038/s41559-020-1127-4&quot;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1038/s41559-020-1127-4&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Andreas Fichtner, Florian Schnabel, Helge Bruelheide, Matthias Kunz, Katharina Mausolf, Andreas Schuldt, Werner Härdtle, and Goddert von Oheimb. 2020. Neighbourhood diversity mitigates drought impacts on tree growth. Journal of Ecology. in publish. &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1111/1365-2745.13353&quot;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1111/1365-2745.13353&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Year" /><summary type="html">Franca J. Bongers, Bernhard Schmid, Zhenkai Sun, Yin Li, Werner Härdtle, Goddert von Oheimb, Ying Li, Shan Li, Michael Staab, Keping Ma, and Xiaojuan Liu. 2020. Growth-trait relationships in subtropical forest are stronger at higher diversity. Journal of Ecology. in publish. https://doi.org/10.1111/1365-2745.13242.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/img/home.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">2019</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="2019" /><published>2018-02-03T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2018-02-03T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/">&lt;p&gt;Philipp Goebes, Karsten Schmidt, Steffen Seitz, Sabine Both, Helge Bruelheide, Alexandra Erfmeier, Thomas Scholten, and Peter Kühn. 2019. The strength of soil-plant interactions under forest is related to a Critical Soil Depth. Scientific Reports. 9:8635. &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1038/s41598-019-45156-5&quot;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1038/s41598-019-45156-5&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Katherina A. Pietsch, David Eichenberg, Karin Nadrowski, Jürgen Bauhus, François Buscot, Witoon Purahong, Benjamin Wipfler, Tesfaye Wubet, Mingjian Yu, and Christian Wirth. 2019. Wood decomposition is more strongly controlled by temperature than by tree species and decomposer diversity in highly species rich subtropical forests. Oikos. 128:701-715. &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1038/s41598-019-45156-5&quot;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1111/oik.04879&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Christian Ristok, Katrin N. Leppert, Michael Scherer-Lorenzen, Pascal A. Niklaus, and Helge Bruelheide. 2019. Soil macrofauna and leaf functional traits drive the decomposition of secondary metabolites in leaf litter. Soil Biology &amp;amp; Biochemistry. 135:429-437. &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1038/s41598-019-45156-5&quot;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.soilbio.2019.06.007&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="GTS" /><summary type="html">Philipp Goebes, Karsten Schmidt, Steffen Seitz, Sabine Both, Helge Bruelheide, Alexandra Erfmeier, Thomas Scholten, and Peter Kühn. 2019. The strength of soil-plant interactions under forest is related to a Critical Soil Depth. Scientific Reports. 9:8635. https://doi.org/10.1038/s41598-019-45156-5.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/home.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">2019</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019XGS/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="2019" /><published>2018-02-01T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2018-02-01T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019XGS</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019XGS/">&lt;p&gt;Helge Bruelheide, Yuxin Chen, Yuanyuan Huang, Keping Ma, Pascal A. Niklaus, and Bernhard Schmid. 2019. Response to Comment on “Impacts of species richness on productivity in a large-scale subtropical forest experiment”. Science. 363:eaav9863. &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1126/science.aav9863&quot;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1126/science.aav9863&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yanjun Du, Bo Yang, Sichong Chen, and Keping Ma. 2019. Diverging shifts in spring phenology in response to biodiversity loss in a subtropical forest. Journal of Vegetation Science. 30:1175-1183. &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1111/jvs.12806&quot;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1111/jvs.12806&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Felix Fornoff, Alexandra-Maria Klein, Nico Bluthgen, and Michael Staab. 2019. Tree diversity increases robustness of multi-trophic interactions. Proceedings of the Royal Society B-Biological Sciences. 286:20182399. &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1098/rspb.2018.2399&quot;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1098/rspb.2018.2399&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;David I. Forrester, Peter Rodenfels, Josephine Haase, Werner Härdtle, Katrin N. Leppert, Pascal A. Niklaus, Goddert von Oheimb, Michael Scherer-Lorenzen, and Jürgen Bauhus. 2019. Tree-species interactions increase light absorption and growth in Chinese subtropical mixedspecies plantations. Oecologia. 191: 421-432. &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1007/s00442-019-04495-w&quot;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1007/s00442-019-04495-w&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Markus S. Germany, Helge Bruelheide, and Alexandra Erfmeier. 2019. Janzen-Connell effects in a forest BEF experiment: Strong distance-dependent seedling establishment of multiple species. Ecology. 100:e02736. &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1002/ecy.2736&quot;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1002/ecy.2736&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Matthias Kunz, Andreas Fichtner, Werner Härdtle, Pasi Raumonen, Helge Bruelheide, and Goddert von Oheimb. 2019. Neighbour species richness and local structural variability modulate aboveground allocation patterns and crown morphology of individual trees. Ecology Letters. 22: 2130-2140. &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1111/ele.13400&quot;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1111/ele.13400&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yin Li, Helge Bruelheide, Thomas Scholten, Bernhard Schmid, Zhenkai Sun, Naili Zhang, Wensheng Bu, Xiaojuan Liu, and Keping Ma. 2019. Early positive effects of tree species richness on soil organic carbon accumulation in a large-scale forest biodiversity experiment. Journal of Plant Ecology. 12:882-893. &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1093/jpe/rtz026&quot;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1093/jpe/rtz026&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tobias Rentschler, Philipp Gries, Thorsten Behrens, Helge Bruelheide, Peter Kühn, Steffen Seitz, Xuezheng Shi, Stefan Trogisch, Thomas Scholten, and Karsten Schmidt. 2019. Comparison of catchment scale 3D and 2.5D modelling of soil organic carbon stocks in Jiangxi Province, PR China. PloS one. 14:e0220881. &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1371/journal.pone.0220881&quot;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1371/journal.pone.0220881&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Christian Ristok, Katrin N. Leppert, Michael Scherer-Lorenzen, Pascal A. Niklaus, and Helge Bruelheide. 2019. Soil macrofauna and leaf functional traits drive the decomposition of secondary metabolites in leaf litter. Soil Biology &amp;amp; Biochemistry. 135:429-437. &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.soilbio.2019.06.007&quot;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.soilbio.2019.06.007&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Andreas Schuldt, Anne Ebeling, Matthias Kunz, Michael Staab, Claudia Guimaraes-Steinicke, Dörte Bachmann, Nina Buchmann, Walter Durka, Andreas Fichtner, Felix Fornoff, Werner Härdtle, Lionel R. Hertzog, Alexandra-Maria Klein, Christiane Roscher, Jörg Schaller, Goddert von Oheimb, Alexandra Weigelt, Wolfgang Weisser, Christian Wirth, Jiayong Zhang, Helge Bruelheide, and Nico Eisenhauer. 2019. Multiple plant diversity components drive consumer communities across ecosystems. Nature Communications. 10:1460. &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1038/s41467-019-09448-8&quot;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1038/s41467-019-09448-8&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Carl J. Skarbek, Merle Noack, Helge Bruelheide, Werner Härdtle, Goddert von Oheimb, Thomas Scholten, Steffen Seitz, and Michael Staab. 2019. A tale of scale: Plot but not neighbourhood tree diversity increases leaf litter ant diversity. Journal of Animal Ecology. in publish. &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1111/1365-2656.13115&quot;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1111/1365-2656.13115&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zhengshan Song, Steffen Seitz, Jian Li, Philipp Goebes, Karsten Schmidt, Peter Kühn, Xuezheng Shi, and Thomas Scholten. 2019. Tree diversity reduced soil erosion by affecting tree canopy and biological soil crust development in a subtropical forest experiment. Forest Ecology and Management. 444:69-77. &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.foreco.2019.04.015&quot;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.foreco.2019.04.015&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mingqiang Wang, Yi Li, Douglas Chesters, Perttu Anttonen, Helge Bruelheide, Jingting Chen, Walter Durka, Pengfei Guo, Werner Härdtle, Keping Ma, Stefan G. Michalski, Bernhard Schmid, Goddert von Oheimb, Chunsheng Wu, Naili Zhang, Qingsong Zhou, Andreas Schuldt, and Chaodong Zhu. 2019. Multiple components of plant diversity loss determine herbivore phylogenetic diversity in a subtropical forest experiment. Journal of Ecology. 107:2697-2712. &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1111/1365-2745.13273&quot;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1111/1365-2745.13273&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Year" /><summary type="html">Helge Bruelheide, Yuxin Chen, Yuanyuan Huang, Keping Ma, Pascal A. Niklaus, and Bernhard Schmid. 2019. Response to Comment on “Impacts of species richness on productivity in a large-scale subtropical forest experiment”. Science. 363:eaav9863. https://doi.org/10.1126/science.aav9863.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/home.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">TreeDì projects</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/treedi.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="TreeDì projects" /><published>2018-02-01T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2018-02-01T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/TreeDi</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/treedi.html">&lt;p&gt;International Research Training Group TreeDì
“TreeDì - 林地 - Tree Diversity Interactions: The role of tree-tree interactions in local neighbourhoods in Chinese subtropical forests” is an International Research Training Group funded by the German Research Foundation (DFG) and the University of Chinese Academy of Sciences (UCAS).
Biodiversity-Ecosystem-Functioning (BEF) research in forests has become a vibrant field of research in the last decade. The aim of TreeDì - 林地 (forest land) is to understand how tree-tree interactions in local neighbourhoods of varying diversity translate into the observed positive tree species richness effects on key ecosystem functions at the community scale. Tree-tree interactions range from above- and belowground competition to resource use complementarity and facilitation. In-depth knowledge of each interaction type and interdisciplinary teamwork are essential to understand the underlying processes. All research projects are carried out on the BEF-China platform in subtropical China - the largest forest BEF experiment worldwide.
For more information about TreeDì projects, go there: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.idiv.de/en/web/treedi/research_projects.html&quot;&gt;https://www.idiv.de/en/web/treedi/research_projects.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>jane</name></author><category term="projects" /><summary type="html">International Research Training Group TreeDì “TreeDì - 林地 - Tree Diversity Interactions: The role of tree-tree interactions in local neighbourhoods in Chinese subtropical forests” is an International Research Training Group funded by the German Research Foundation (DFG) and the University of Chinese Academy of Sciences (UCAS). Biodiversity-Ecosystem-Functioning (BEF) research in forests has become a vibrant field of research in the last decade. The aim of TreeDì - 林地 (forest land) is to understand how tree-tree interactions in local neighbourhoods of varying diversity translate into the observed positive tree species richness effects on key ecosystem functions at the community scale. Tree-tree interactions range from above- and belowground competition to resource use complementarity and facilitation. In-depth knowledge of each interaction type and interdisciplinary teamwork are essential to understand the underlying processes. All research projects are carried out on the BEF-China platform in subtropical China - the largest forest BEF experiment worldwide. For more information about TreeDì projects, go there: https://www.idiv.de/en/web/treedi/research_projects.html</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/home.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Other ongoing projects</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/otherprojects.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Other ongoing projects" /><published>2018-01-15T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2018-01-15T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/OtherProjects</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/otherprojects.html">&lt;details&gt;
&lt;summary class=&quot;dropdown-text&quot;&gt; The effects of tree species diversity on productivity and turnover of different fine-root functional groups&lt;/summary&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;dropdown-sub&quot;&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Principal Investigator:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
Assist. Prof. Dr. ZhenKai Sun&lt;br /&gt;  	
Research Institute of Forestry, Chinese Academy of Forestry&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-envelope&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; sunzhenkai1987&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-at&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;163.com
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;

&lt;details&gt;
&lt;summary class=&quot;dropdown-text&quot;&gt; Influence of local biodiversity on the seasonality of tree growth&lt;/summary&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;dropdown-sub&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Principal Investigator:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Assoc. Prof. Dr. Zhiyao Tang&lt;br /&gt;
College of Urban and Environmental Sciences, Peking University&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-envelope&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; zytang&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-at&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;urban.pku.edu.cn&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;PhD student: Gheyur Gheyret&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;

&lt;details&gt;
&lt;summary class=&quot;dropdown-text&quot;&gt; The effects of contrasting climatic conditions on diversity-stability relationships&lt;/summary&gt;&lt;br /&gt; 	
&lt;li class=&quot;dropdown-sub&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Principal Investigators:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
Prof. Dr. Christian Wirth&lt;br /&gt;
Institute of Biology, Leipzig University (UL) &amp;amp; iDiv&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-envelope&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; cwirth&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-at&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;uni-leipzig.de&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;PhD student: Florian Schnabel&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;

&lt;details&gt;
&lt;summary class=&quot;dropdown-text&quot;&gt; Role of intra- and inter-specific species traits values in the genetic diversity effect on tree growth and forest productivity in the 4x1 genetic experiment&lt;/summary&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;dropdown-sub&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Principal Investigators:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
Assoc. Prof. Dr. Xiaojuan Liu&lt;br /&gt;
Institute of Botany, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-envelope&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; liuxiaojuan06&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-at&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;ibcas.ac.cn&lt;br /&gt;
Prof. Dr. Keping Ma&lt;br /&gt;
Institute of Botany, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-envelope&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; kpma&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-at&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;ibcas.ac.cn&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Postdoc: Dr. Franca J Bongers&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;

&lt;details&gt;
&lt;summary class=&quot;dropdown-text&quot;&gt; Tree growth under a gradient of species diversity, considering intra-specific genetic variation of 12 species&lt;/summary&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;dropdown-sub&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Principal Investigators:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Assoc. Prof. Dr. Xiaojuan Liu&lt;br /&gt;
Institute of Botany, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-envelope&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; liuxiaojuan06&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-at&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;ibcas.ac.cn&lt;br /&gt;
Prof. Dr. Keping Ma&lt;br /&gt;
Institute of Botany, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-envelope&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; kpma&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-at&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;ibcas.ac.cn&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Postdoc: Dr. Franca J Bongers&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;

&lt;details&gt;
&lt;summary class=&quot;dropdown-text&quot;&gt; The role of community trait identity and trait diversity on forest productivity, considering different species extinction scenarios&lt;/summary&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;dropdown-sub&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Principal Investigators:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Assoc. Prof. Dr. Xiaojuan Liu&lt;br /&gt;
Institute of Botany, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-envelope&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; liuxiaojuan06&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-at&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;ibcas.ac.cn&lt;br /&gt;
Prof. Dr. Keping Ma&lt;br /&gt;
Institute of Botany, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-envelope&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; kpma&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-at&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;ibcas.ac.cn&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Postdoc: Dr. Franca J Bongers&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;

&lt;details&gt;
&lt;summary class=&quot;dropdown-text&quot;&gt; The richness effect on tree and shrub survival in the BEF-China experiment&lt;/summary&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;dropdown-sub&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Principal Investigators:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Assoc. Prof. Dr. Xiaojuan Liu&lt;br /&gt;
Institute of Botany, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-envelope&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; liuxiaojuan06&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-at&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;ibcas.ac.cn&lt;br /&gt;
Prof. Dr. Keping Ma&lt;br /&gt;
Institute of Botany, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-envelope&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; kpma&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-at&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;ibcas.ac.cn&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Postdoc: Dr. Shan Li&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;

&lt;details&gt;
&lt;summary class=&quot;dropdown-text&quot;&gt; Assessing the dynamic of vegetation function and productivity with laser and hyperspectral analyses of CSPs and main experiments&lt;/summary&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;dropdown-sub&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Principal Investigators:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
Assoc. Prof. Dr. Xiaojuan Liu&lt;br /&gt;
Institute of Botany, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-envelope&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; liuxiaojuan06&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-at&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;ibcas.ac.cn&lt;br /&gt;
Prof. Dr. Bernhard Schmid&lt;br /&gt;
University of Zurich&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-envelope&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; bernhard.schmid&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-at&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;ieu.uzh.ch&lt;br /&gt;
Prof. Dr. Keping Ma&lt;br /&gt;
Institute of Botany, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-envelope&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; kpma&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-at&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;ibcas.ac.cn&lt;br /&gt;
Prof. Dr. Michael E. Schaepman&lt;br /&gt;
University of Zurich&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-envelope&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; michael.schaepman&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-at&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;geo.uzh.ch&lt;br /&gt;	 
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;

&lt;details&gt;
&lt;summary class=&quot;dropdown-text&quot;&gt; The effect of wood stumps on soil organic carbon accumulation&lt;/summary&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;dropdown-sub&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Principal Investigators:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Assoc. Prof. Dr. Yin Li	Sanming University&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-envelope&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; lijiang413508&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-at&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;126.com
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;

&lt;details&gt;
&lt;summary class=&quot;dropdown-text&quot;&gt; Probing soil organic carbon composition and dynamics in the rhizosphere and bulk soil of Gutianshan&lt;/summary&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;dropdown-sub&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Principal Investigators:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Prof. Dr. Xiaojuan Feng&lt;br /&gt;
Institute of Botany, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-envelope&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; xfeng&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-at&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;ibcas.ac.cn&lt;br /&gt;
Assist. Prof. Dr. Yufu Jia&lt;br /&gt;
Institute of Botany, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-envelope&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; yufu123jia&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-at&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;163.com&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;

&lt;details&gt;
&lt;summary class=&quot;dropdown-text&quot;&gt; Formation and dynamics of mineral-associated organic carbon in subtropical forests&lt;/summary&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;dropdown-sub&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Principal Investigators:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Prof. Dr. Xiaojuan Feng	Institute of Botany, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-envelope&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; xfeng&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-at&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;ibcas.ac.cn&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;PhD student: Zongguang Liu&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;

&lt;details&gt;
&lt;summary class=&quot;dropdown-text&quot;&gt; Effects of plant diversity on greenhouse gas fluxes and associated microbial mechanisms in soils of a subtropical forest&lt;/summary&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;dropdown-sub&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Principal Investigators:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Prof. Dr. Xiaoqi Zhou&lt;br /&gt;
School of Ecological and Environmental Sciences, East China Normal University&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-envelope&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; xqzhou&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-at&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;des.ecnu.edu.cn
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;

&lt;details&gt;
&lt;summary class=&quot;dropdown-text&quot;&gt; Host-parasitoid interaction	&lt;/summary&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;dropdown-sub&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Principal Investigators:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Chaodong Zhu&lt;br /&gt;
Institute of Zoology, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-envelope&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; zhucd&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-at&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;ioz.ac.cn&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;PhD student: Pengfei Guo&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;

&lt;details&gt;
&lt;summary class=&quot;dropdown-text&quot;&gt; The interaction between soil mite and tree diversity; The responses of soil mite diversity to different tree species.&lt;/summary&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;dropdown-sub&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Principal Investigators:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Prof. Dr. Chaodong Zhu&lt;br /&gt;
Institute of Zoology, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-envelope&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; zhucd&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-at&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; ioz.ac.cn &lt;br /&gt;
Prof. Dr. Jun Chen&lt;br /&gt;
Institute of Zoology, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-envelope&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; chenj&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-at&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;ioz.ac.cn&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Master student: Yannan Chen&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;

&lt;details&gt;
&lt;summary class=&quot;dropdown-text&quot;&gt; Effects of tree and shrub species diversity on leaf litter decomposition and microbial decomposers communities inhabiting in litter&lt;/summary&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;dropdown-sub&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Principal Investigators:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Assoc. Prof. Dr. Naili Zhang&lt;br /&gt;
Institute of Botany, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-envelope&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; zhangnl&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-at&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;ibcas.ac.cn&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Postdoc: Dr. Hong Lin&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;

&lt;details&gt;
&lt;summary class=&quot;dropdown-text&quot;&gt; Indirect effects of tree richness and species identity drive plant growth in subtropical forest&lt;/summary&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;dropdown-sub&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Principal Investigators:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Assoc. Prof. Dr. Naili Zhang&lt;br /&gt;
Institute of Botany, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-envelope&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; zhangnl&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-at&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;ibcas.ac.cn&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Postdoc: Dr. Hong Lin&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;

&lt;details&gt;
&lt;summary class=&quot;dropdown-text&quot;&gt; How does the association of tree species richness with litter fungal community change with time&lt;/summary&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;dropdown-sub&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Principal Investigators:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Assoc. Prof. Dr. Naili Zhang&lt;br /&gt;
Institute of Botany, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-envelope&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; zhangnl&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-at&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;ibcas.ac.cn&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Master student: Xinlei Zhang&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;

&lt;details&gt;
&lt;summary class=&quot;dropdown-text&quot;&gt; The effects of host plant diversity on the assembly of phylloesphere microbial communities&lt;/summary&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;dropdown-sub&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Principal Investigators:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Prof. Dr. Lin Jiang	Georgia&lt;br /&gt;
Institute of Technology&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-envelope&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; lin.jiang&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-at&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;biology.gatech.edu&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;PhD student: Xian Yang&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;

&lt;details&gt;
&lt;summary class=&quot;dropdown-text&quot;&gt; How biodiversity-ecosystem functioning relations change with or without the presence of local soil biota&lt;/summary&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;dropdown-sub&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Principal Investigators:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Dr. Sylvia Haider&lt;br /&gt;
Institute of Biology / Geobotany, MLU &amp;amp; iDiv；&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-envelope&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; sylvia.haider&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-at&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;botanik.uni-halle.de&lt;br /&gt;
Dr. Yang Bo	&lt;br /&gt;
Jingdezhen University	&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-envelope&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; yangbomvp&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-at&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;aliyun.com&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;

&lt;details&gt;
&lt;summary class=&quot;dropdown-text&quot;&gt; Do trees with extrafloral nectaries interact with tree diversity in mediating insect communities, leaf damage, defense traits and tree growth?&lt;/summary&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;dropdown-sub&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Principal Investigators:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Assoc. Prof. Dr. Xiaojuan Liu&lt;br /&gt;
Institute of Botany, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-envelope&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; liuxiaojuan06&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-at&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;ibcas.ac.cn&lt;br /&gt;
Assoc. Prof. Dr. Naili Zhang&lt;br /&gt;
Institute of Botany, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-envelope&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; zhangnl&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-at&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;ibcas.ac.cn&lt;br /&gt;
Assoc. Prof. Dr. Michael Staab&lt;br /&gt;
University of Freiburg&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-envelope&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; michael.staab&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-at&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;nature.uni-freiburg.de&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Master student: Stefanie Pietsch&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;

&lt;details&gt;
&lt;summary class=&quot;dropdown-text&quot;&gt; Dispersal of pathogens in forest stand with different tree diversity&lt;/summary&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;dropdown-sub&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Principal Investigators:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Assoc. Prof. Dr. Yu Liang&lt;br /&gt;
Institute of Botany, Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-envelope&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; coolrain&lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-at&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;ibcas.ac.cn&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Master student: Shaoran Li&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/details&gt;</content><author><name>jane</name></author><category term="projects" /><summary type="html">The effects of tree species diversity on productivity and turnover of different fine-root functional groups Principal Investigator: Assist. Prof. Dr. ZhenKai Sun Research Institute of Forestry, Chinese Academy of Forestry sunzhenkai1987163.com</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/img/home.jpg" /></entry></feed>